<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>tese</title>
    <link href="https://kouhu1.github.io/hoiho/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://kouhu1.github.io/hoiho" />
    <updated>2023-02-23T22:21:44+00:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>hu</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://kouhu1.github.io/hoiho</id>

    <entry>
        <title>City of London</title>
        <author>
            <name>hu</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://kouhu1.github.io/hoiho/city-of-london.html"/>
        <id>https://kouhu1.github.io/hoiho/city-of-london.html</id>
        <media:content url="https://kouhu1.github.io/hoiho/media/posts/2/buildings-g5e6013f40_640-2.jpg" medium="image" />

        <updated>2023-02-23T22:21:44+00:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://kouhu1.github.io/hoiho/media/posts/2/buildings-g5e6013f40_640-2.jpg" alt="" />
                    A walking tour of the City of London is a fantastic way to explore the rich history and cultural significance&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://kouhu1.github.io/hoiho/media/posts/2/buildings-g5e6013f40_640-2.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <p>A walking tour of the City of London is a fantastic way to explore the rich history and cultural significance of this ancient city. The tour typically begins at the Tower of London, one of the most iconic landmarks in London, before proceeding to other famous attractions such as St. Paul's Cathedral, the Bank of England, and the historic Guildhall.</p>
<p>As you walk through the narrow streets and winding alleys, your guide will share fascinating stories and insights about the city's past, from the Roman era to the present day. You'll learn about the Great Fire of London, the Blitz during World War II, and the City's role as a financial center.</p>
<p>Other highlights of the tour may include visiting medieval churches and crypts, exploring hidden alleyways, and discovering beautiful public squares and gardens. Whether you're a first-time visitor or a seasoned traveler, a walking tour of the City of London is an excellent way to experience the unique culture and history of this vibrant city.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>St. Paul Cathedral </title>
        <author>
            <name>hu</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://kouhu1.github.io/hoiho/st-paul-cathedral.html"/>
        <id>https://kouhu1.github.io/hoiho/st-paul-cathedral.html</id>

        <updated>2023-02-23T22:17:29+00:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    A tour of St. Paul's Cathedral in London is a must-see for visitors interested in history, art, and architecture. The&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://kouhu1.github.io/hoiho/media/posts/1/london-g2be192357_640.jpg" alt="" width="640" height="360" sizes="(max-width: 48em) 100vw, 100vw" srcset="https://kouhu1.github.io/hoiho/media/posts/1/responsive/london-g2be192357_640-xs.jpg 300w ,https://kouhu1.github.io/hoiho/media/posts/1/responsive/london-g2be192357_640-sm.jpg 480w ,https://kouhu1.github.io/hoiho/media/posts/1/responsive/london-g2be192357_640-md.jpg 768w"></figure>
<p>A tour of St. Paul's Cathedral in London is a must-see for visitors interested in history, art, and architecture. The cathedral is one of the most iconic buildings in London and has played an important role in the city's history since its construction in the 17th century.</p>
<p>During the tour, visitors can explore the magnificent interior of the cathedral, including the impressive nave, choir, and altar. They can also climb the famous dome and enjoy breathtaking views of London from the top. Additionally, visitors can learn about the history of the cathedral and its role in significant events such as the funerals of Sir Winston Churchill and the Duke of Wellington.</p>
<p>The tour is led by knowledgeable guides who can provide insights into the history, architecture, and religious significance of the cathedral. With its stunning design and rich history, a tour of St. Paul's Cathedral is a must-see experience for any visitor to London.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
